A Guide to the Papers of Ann Beattie
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Ann Beattie 1982-1984
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
10414-l
This collection consists of 49 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was deposited on 1987 March 30
Scope and Content Information
Collection includes master proof and typed manuscript copy of Where you'll find me and other stories; drafts and proofs of articles and interviews by and about Beattie; drafts of several of her short stories; and publicity material for her books and lectures.
Also include letters from various publishing houses requesting Beattie's opinion of new books; a review of Spectacles; and a manuscript of Elizabeth Tallent's Time with children.
Contents List
- Books
  - Where You'll Find Me And Other Stories 1986, copy TMs
    edited manuscript
  - Where You'll Find Me And Other Stories 1986, Master Proof
- Miscellaneous Manuscripts
  - A reading(?) re books, early draft ca. 1986, TMs
    (eventually published in Leisure Magazine)
  - Article re books, Leisure Magazine1986 Sep, Computer Print-Out
  - Essay on a Timothy Kelly Story, "The Tape Recorder" 1987, TMs
    w/corrections
  - "Five Minutes with Ann Beattie" 1986, Galley Proof
    with a letter from John Atwood, editor of Eastern Review
  - Untitled article 1986?, TMs
  - Untitled article 1986?, Computer Print-Out
    w/corrections and editorial comments
  - Time With Children by Elizabeth Tallent ca. 1986, TMs (electrostatic copy and galley proofs)
    w/corrections and a letter from "Anton"
- Short Stories
  - "Amalfi" 1986 Aug, Author's Proof
  - "Horatio's Trick" n.d., TMs
    early draft
  - "Horatio's Trick" n.d., TMs
    revised draft
  - "Imagine a Day at the End of Your Life" n.d., TMs
  - "Jefferson, Seeing the Sun" n.d., TMs
  - "Performances" n.d., TMs
    early drafts w/corrections
  - "Perfornances" ("Performens") n.d., TMs
- Letters and Miscellaneous
  - "Where You'll Find Me" 1986 March, Electrostatic Copy
    edited manuscript (used for Where You'll Find Me And Other Stories?)
  - Letters to Ann Beattie 1982, 1986-1987
  - Reviews and Publicity 1985-1986